bollycurry.com 2009-06-03

# India-Forums -Privacy Policy

**About India-forums.com**

India-Forums.com is the # 1 Discussion Forums with more than 330,000 members currently (June, 2008) and was started in December 2003.  From the days of _**Jassi Jaissi Koi Nahi**_ \- India-Forums has succeeded in bringing together television viewers all across the globe. It has merged the virtual world and reality in a beautiful combination where virtual friends are now part of an extended family with many special bonds and relationships. India-Forums started as television discussion forum has branched out to several other sections like Bollywood, Tellybuzz, Celebrity Interview, Internet Radio, Fan Clubs, Debate Mansion, Sports, Books Talk, Fashion News update and Gizmo Talks.

India-Forums is the leading Indian Website and is currently in the top 15 High Traffic Indian Website according to [Big-Boards.com](http://www.big-boards.com/highlight/1412/traffic/) It is also positioned in top 5 websites in terms of daily [pageviews](http://www.big-boards.com/highlight/1412/pageviews/). In terms of Alexa ranking (Amazon based company) India-Forum is at top 2,000 website in the world. With the new features adding in continuously and the support and active participation of its members India-Forum is progressing at a breakneck speed with surely sky is a limit.

India-forums.com is an online youth networking site, owned and managed by **Cyberax Media Pvt. Ltd.** registered members are allowed to set up unique personal profiles that can be linked together through networks of friends. India-forums members can view each others' profiles with the objective of making new friends, communicating with old friends, sharing photos and posting journals and comments etc. **In order to ensure that the objectives of the site can be fulfilled to the satisfaction of India-forums members** , we request and display some personal information / profile information relating to one or more members to other members and visitors, which allows our users to identify each other and expand their network of friends. India-forums members can change their personal information and/or profile information at any time. Kindly note that although most of the online services are offered for free, users would require a "Mandatory Registration" to navigate and use India-forums services. To know more about the said "Mandatory Registration", please follow the link below: <http://www.india-forums.com/terms_of_use.asp>

India-forums.com respects the privacy of users and is committed to protect their privacy in all respects. Should you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please email us at Privacy Policy.

The present privacy policy governs the online information collection practices of India-forums.com ("we" or "us" or "India-forums"). Specifically, it outlines the types of information that we gather about you from your use of the India-forums.com website (the "Site"), and the ways in which we use and don't use this information. This privacy policy, including our children's privacy statement, does not apply to any information you may provide to us or that we may collect offline and/or through other means. To register for full access to the Site and in certain areas of the Site (for example, on contest entry pages), where personal information is requested, you may be asked for your age or birth date. You hereby agree that all information you provide to India-forums regarding age verification shall be truthful, accurate, and complete.

This privacy policy details important information regarding the use and disclosure of user and/ or member information collected on the Site. India-forums provides this privacy policy to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or discontinue using the Site.

This privacy policy is incorporated into and is subject to the India-forums [Terms of Use](http://www.india-forums.com/terms_of_use.asp). Your use of the India-forums Site and any personal information you provide on the Site remains subject to the terms of this privacy policy and our [Terms of Use](http://www.india-forums.com/terms_of_use.asp).

Please note that any video, image, comment or other content posted on the Site becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information which is subject to this privacy notice.

Please read this privacy policy carefully. By visiting and using the Site, you agree that your use of the Site, and any dispute over privacy, is governed by this privacy policy and our **Terms of Use** at the following link: [Terms of Use](http://www.india-forums.com/terms_of_use.asp).

**WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED ABOUT OUR USERS AND MEMBERS?**

The information that we collect about you while you are using the Site falls into the following general categories:

 **INVITATIONS AND OTHER COMMUNICATIONS TO NON-MEMBERS**

India-forums members can invite friends to join the service by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation system. The India-forums Site stores the email addresses that members provide so that the respondents may be added to the friend's list of the member sending the invitations, and also to send reminders of the invitations. The India-forums Site does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations, invitation reminders (up to three (3) per email address). Recipients of invitations from India-forums may contact the India-forums Site to request the removal of their information from our database.

India-forums members may also store email addresses of people they know in their internal India-forums address book and may also choose to send invitations and other communications to those addresses.

You may prevent email invitations from us by sending a single email with the subject "BLOCK" to Unsubscribe. Please note that the email must come from the account you wish to block.

**OUR COMMITMENT TO CHILDRENS' PRIVACY**

The Site is NOT directed to or intended for people under the age of sixteen. A User less than 16 (Sixteen) years of age should not register to use the Site. India-forums do not knowingly collect any personal information from people under the age of sixteen. If you are a parent of a child under the age of sixteen and you have questions about our Site or Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact the India-forums Privacy Coordinator at Privacy Policy.  
Those between the age of sixteen and eighteen are to provide either of their parents Email ID and an Email will be send informing that their ward has registered himself/herself to use the India-forums.com services. The parent will be legally bound by any acts/deeds/Violation of India-forums.com [Terms of Use](http://www.india-forums.com/terms_of_use.asp) & Privacy Policy by their wards.

**OUR COMMITMENT TO DATA SECURITY**

We use commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to India-forums and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, India-forums makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

If India-forums learn of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. India-forums may post a notice on the India-forums Site if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify us using this link Privacy Policy.

**SPECIAL NOTE TO INTERNATIONAL USERS / MEMBERS**

India-forums is hosted in India and is intended for and directed to users / members in India. If you are a user / member accessing the India-forums Site from any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, protection and disclosure, that differ from Indian laws, please be advised that through your use of the India-forums Site, this Privacy Notice, and our [Terms of Use](http://www.india-forums.com/terms_of_use.asp), you are transferring your personal information to India and you consent to that transfer. We will only be complying with the legal provisions on the subject matter as applicable in India from time to time.

**HOW YOU CAN MAKE CHANGES TO YOUR INFORMATION**

**NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES:**  
We reserve the right at any time to: change the terms of this Agreement; change the Services, including eliminating or modifying any content on or feature of the Site; or change/charge any fees or charges for use of the Services.  
Any changes we make will be effective immediately on notice, which we may give either by posting the new Agreement on the Site or via electronic mail. Your use of the Services after such notice will be deemed acceptance of such changes. Be sure to review this Agreement periodically to ensure your familiarity with the most current version. You will always be able to tell when the version was last updated by checking the "Last Revised" date in the header of this agreement.

**CONFLICT RESOLUTION:**  
We are committed to resolving disputes as soon as feasible and shall endeavor to resolve all disputes brought to our notice in keeping with the mechanism prescribed, within 15 working days of such receipt.

**CONTACT INFORMATION**  
If site users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:  
E-mail: Support   
Telephone: +91 22 4016 6640  
Postal address: Midas Chambers, Unit No. 601, 6th Floor, Off Link Road, Near Fun Republic, Opposite Yash Raj Films, Andheri (W), Mumbai.

**WEBSITE ADMINISTRATION**  
Business name: Cyberax Media Pvt. Ltd.  
Address: Midas Chambers, Unit No. 601, 6th Floor, Off Link Road, Near Fun Republic, Opposite Yash Raj Films, Andheri (W),  
City: Mumbai  
State: Maharashtra  
Pin code: 400 053  
Country: India  
Website URL: http://www.India-forums.com
